http://www.nitek.net/privacystatement/

PERSONAL DATA IS PROCESSED
Nitek may process personal data about you, because you make use of the services of, and / or because you provide it yourself when filling out a contact form on the website. Nitek can process the following personal data:
Your first and last name
Your address details
Your phone number
Your email address
Your IP address
WHY NITEK NEEDS DATA
Nitek processes your personal data to be able to contact you by telephone if you request it, and / or to be able to contact you in writing (by e-mail and / or by post)
approach if you cannot be reached by telephone.
In addition, Nitek may use your personal data in the context of informing by means of newsletters and / or executing an agreement determined with you of a quotation or order placed at Nitek.
HOW LONG NITEK SAVES YOUR DATA
Nitek does not store your personal data longer than is strictly necessary to achieve the goals for which your data is collected. If you yourself indicate in writing that you no longer wish to be a contact in our database, you will be removed from our database.
SHARE WITH OTHERS
Nitek will only provide your personal data to third parties if this is necessary for the execution of an agreement with you, or to comply with a legal obligation.
REGISTER WEBSITE VISIT
General visitor data are kept on the Nitek website,
including the IP address of your computer and the time of retrieval and data that your browser sends. This data is used for analyzes of visitor and click behavior on the website. Nitek uses this information to improve the operation of the website. This data is anonymized as much as possible and is not provided to third parties.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
Nitek uses Google Analytics to track how users use the Nitek website and how effective the Ad-words ads are from Google search result pages.
The information thus obtained, including the address of your computer (IP address),
transferred to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.
Read Google’s privacy policy for more information.
You also find the privacy policy of Google Analytics here.
Google uses this information to keep track of how our website is used, to provide reports on the Website to Nitek and to provide its advertisers with information about the effectiveness of their campaigns.
Google may provide this information to third parties if Google is legally obliged to do so, or insofar as these third parties process the information on behalf of Google.
Nitek has no influence on this.
Nitek has not granted Google permission to use Analytics information obtained through Nitek for other Google services.
SEE, CUSTOMIZE OR REMOVAL DATA
You have the right to view, correct or delete your personal data. You can send a request for access, correction or deletion to media@nitek.net. Nitek will respond to your request as soon as possible, but within four weeks.
Menu
Home
Products
For UTP Cabling
For Coax Cabling
For Fiber Cabling
Surge Protection
For Analog Devices
